Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this quick video, we would want to look at a couple of alternatives for the String class.
在这个快速视频中，我们想看看String类的几个替代方案。
One of the problems with the String class is String is immutable.
String类的一个问题是String是不可变的。
So, as soon as I create a string like this, let's say I am doing "123" + "123" +"1234"+
所以，只要我创建一个这样的字符串，比如说我在做 "123"+"123"+"1234"+
"123456". Think about how many strings we are creating.
"123456". 想想看，我们正在创建多少个字符串。
So, this creates the entire concatenated string.
所以，这就创建了整个串联的字符串。
So, when we are doing this operation, what we are doing is, we are creating individual string instances
所以，当我们做这个操作时，我们正在做的是，我们正在创建单独的字符串实例
for 1, 2, 3, and 4. So, four values in here. Because the concatenation runs from left to right, first
1、2、3、4的单个字符串实例。所以，这里有四个值。因为连接是从左到右进行的，首先
these two are concatenated and 123 + 123 becomes  123123.
这两个被连接起来，123+123变成123123。
So, this is the 5th instance
所以，这是第五个实例
and after that another instance concatenating all these three and sixth instance and then a seventh
之后是另一个实例，将这三个值串联起来，然后是第六个实例和第七个实例。
instance.
实例。
So, just to do a simple concatenation, we had to create seven instances of this string, right. The first
所以，只是为了做一个简单的连接，我们必须为这个字符串创建七个实例，对吧。前面的
four are definitely needed because those are values, but there are three additional instances of objects
前四个是绝对需要的，因为这些是值，但还有三个额外的对象实例
that are being created
正在被创建
and that's a very costly operation. Creating objects
而这是一个非常昂贵的操作。创建对象
is very very costly.
是非常非常昂贵的。
If this is the case, if it's four simple strings,
如果是这种情况，如果是四个简单的字符串。
but imagine the case when I have to append 200 strings. How many useless objects would be created? To avoid
但想象一下，如果我不得不追加200个字符串。会有多少无用的对象被创建？为了避免
that, Java provides another class called StringBuffer.
Java提供了另一个叫做StringBuffer的类。
So, StringBuffer is another class in Java which you can use to create strings.
所以，StringBuffer是Java中的另一个类，你可以用它来创建字符串。
However StringBuffer is not as easy to use as a String, right. So,
然而StringBuffer并不像String那样容易使用，对吧。所以。
if it was a String, I can just say this. Oops!
如果它是一个字符串，我就可以这样说。Oops!
That's not allowed with a StringBuffer. You have to actually use new StringBuffer
这在StringBuffer中是不允许的。你必须实际使用new StringBuffer
("TEst")
The important thing is StringBuffer is mutable.
重要的是，StringBuffer是可变的。
That means if I do a sb. let's say, append and say append("123") and I leave a space in here.
这意味着如果我做一个sb.比方说，append，说append("123")，我在这里留下一个空格。
What would happen? sb
会发生什么？
value also gets changed. So, sb new have, sb has the new value, right. Now,
值也会被改变。所以，sb新的有，sb有新的值，对。现在。
so the value inside the string buffer is changing.
所以字符串缓冲区内的值是变化的。
So, it's actually saying "TEst 123". sb.setCharAt, let's say I would want to replace this character
所以，它实际上是在说 "TEst 123"。sb.setCharAt，假设我想把这个字符替换为
with a 'e'. So, I can say charAt, index is
用一个'e'。所以，我可以说charAt，索引是
(1,'e').
Now, if I do sb, it would show "TEst 123" because we have replaced this character.
现在，如果我做sb，它将显示 "TEst 123"，因为我们已经替换了这个字符。
One thing you would notice that with StringBuffer is that, we are actually changing the value inside
你会注意到StringBuffer的一个特点是，我们实际上是在改变StringBuffer里面的值。
the StringBuffer .
StringBuffer。
So, that's an important thing.
所以，这是一个重要的事情。
So, in StringBuffer you can actually change the values. Whenever you do a lot of concatenations,
所以，在StringBuffer中，你实际上可以改变值。每当你做大量的连接时。
it's preferred that you'd use a StringBuffer.
你最好使用一个StringBuffer。
There is another class which is offered in Java which is called StringBuilder. StringBuilder is
在Java中还有一个类，它被称为StringBuilder。StringBuilder是
very very similar to StringBuffer. But it's offered in the later versions of Java because StringBuffer is
与StringBuffer非常相似。但它是在Java的后期版本中提供的，因为StringBuffer是一个
a synchronised class.
一个同步的类。
So, what does that mean?
那么，这意味着什么呢？
That means, that StringBuffer is a class which is ready for multithreading. But if you are ready for
这意味着，StringBuffer是一个可以用于多线程的类。但如果你准备好了
multithreading, it means that there is a penalty which is imposed on you.
多线程，就意味着有一个惩罚是强加给你的。
That means when you're running in a single-threaded scenarios where you don't really need all the complexities
这意味着当你在一个单线程的场景中运行时，你并不真的需要所有关于多线程的复杂问题
around multithreading, StringBuffer might get really slow and in those kind of situations, you can use
围绕多线程，StringBuffer可能会变得非常慢，在这种情况下，你可以使用
StringBuilder.
StringBuilder。
We'd talk about multithreading and all that kind of stuff a little later in this course in a separate
我们将在本课程稍后的单独章节中讨论多线程和所有这些东西。
section.
节中讨论多线程和所有这些东西。
But for now, you can think that if you don't really worry about multithreading, then you can use a String
但是现在，你可以认为，如果你不太担心多线程，那么你可以使用一个String
Builder.
生成器。
So, instead of a StringBuffer, you can use a StringBuilder. So, I can say StringBuilder sb =
所以，你可以使用一个StringBuffer，而不是一个StringBuilder。所以，我可以说StringBuilder sb =
new StringBuilder with your string.
new StringBuilder与你的字符串。
If you further explore the APIs of StringBuffer and String Builder, you would see that there are
如果你进一步探索StringBuffer和String Builder的API，你会发现它们提供的方法是有变化的。
variations in the methods that they offer and things like that.
它们所提供的方法和类似的东西是不同的。
But effectively, the thing which you'd need to remember is this. If you're concatenating a lot of strings
但实际上，你需要记住的是这一点。如果你要串联大量的字符串
and creating a lot of instances of strings, then it's recommended to go for the alternatives, either the
并创建大量的字符串实例，那么建议你选择其他的方法，要么选择
StringBuilder or the StringBuffer. If you don't worry about multithreading, then you would really be
StringBuilder或StringBuffer。如果你不担心多线程的问题，那么你真的会被建议使用
advised to go with the StringBuilder class. If you want your code to be thread-safe, then you'd go for
建议你使用StringBuilder类。如果你希望你的代码是线程安全的，那么你会选择
the StringBuffer
StringBuffer
class. We will discuss more about multithreading when we encounter that in a subsequent section.
类。当我们在后面的章节中遇到多线程时，我们将讨论更多关于多线程的问题。
In this video, we discussed the alternatives to String, StringBuilder, and StringBuffer and things
在这个视频中，我们讨论了String、StringBuilder和StringBuffer的替代品，以及类似的东西。
like that.
诸如此类的东西。
I'll see you in the next video.
我们将在下一个视频中见。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，拜拜了。